Guide to the Ephemera collection, 1835-2002 MS2380
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Ephemera collection
1835-2002
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
MS2380
4.5 Linear Feet 8 document boxes and 1 flat box
This is an artificial collection composed of printed materials acquired by Special Collections Research Center at various times. The collection was created in 2018 from original MARC records. The collection contains magazines, printed materials, and paper documents related primarily to the history of Washington DC and the Metropolitan area. More broadly the subject is American History. The images date from approximately 1835-2002.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
Organized in two series: Oversize ephemera [formerly flat folio] and Ephemera. These series are devised from the original location codes used in the ILS.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials acquired over time from many sources.
Scope and Contents
This collection is composed of publication, portions of publicatons and other printed materials. These materials were originally individually cataloged and managed in the library's ILS. The primary subject of the materials is the history of Washington DC and the Metropolitan area. More broadly the subject is American History. The items date from approximately 1835-2002.
Biographical / Historical
This is an artificial collection composed of printed materials acquired by Special Collections Research Center at various times. The collection was created in 2018 from original MARC records.
- Oversize ephemera [formerly flat folios], 1846-1998; Series 1
  Arrangement
  Arranged in original call no. order.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains publications and printed materials covering the history of Washington DC and the Metropolitan area. More broadly the subject is American History. The images date from approximately 1835-2002.
  - In wartime Washington: intimate glimpses of our war-makers and lawmakers: how the capital is measuring up to the national crisis by Edward Hungerford., Circa [1917]; Series 1; pages 13-16, 43-44: illustrations, portraits; 32 cm (Box 9, Folder 1)
    General
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 208 FF
    Cataloging notes: Caption title.; Detached from: Travel. August, 1917.
    Subjects: World War (1914-1918) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01180746; 1914 - 1918 fast; World War, 1914-1918 Washington (D.C.); Washington (D.C.) History. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145352; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; History. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01411628
  - [Articles about Washington, D.C.]., Circa 1869-1892.; Series 1; pages 454-455, 219-221, 328-330, 375-376, 5-6; 124-125; 31 cm (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 209 FF
    Cataloging notes: Caption titles.; Detached from: The Nation. No. 230 (Nov. 25, 1869); No. 300 (Mar. 30, 1871); No. 386 (Nov. 21, 1872); No. 467 (June 11, 1874); No. 497 (Jan. 7, 1875); Vol. 54, No. 1390 (Feb. 18, 1892).; Men and things in Washington -- Washington before the Rebellion -- A new experiment in city government -- How shall we govern the national capital? -- The condition of the District of Columbia -- Our national observatory.
    Subjects: United States Naval Observatory. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n78095580; United States Naval Observatory. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00528874; To 1878 fast; Politics and government fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01919741; Washington (D.C.) History. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145352; Washington (D.C.) Politics and government To 1878. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145357; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; History. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01411628
  - Completion of the Washington Monument., Circa [1884]; Series 1; pages [277]; 32 cm (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 247 FF
    Cataloging notes: Caption title.; Detached from: The American architect and building news. Vol. 16, numbers 468 (Dec. 13, 1884).
    Subjects: Washington Monument (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh86000926; Washington Monument (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01170927
  - American motorist. Vol. 6, numbers 6 (September 1931)., Circa [1931]; Series 1; 48 pages: illustrations; 30 cm (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 318 FF
    Cataloging notes: Issue of the District of Columbia edition of the periodical.; Teaing and dining 'round Washington -- A new campus [of George Washington University] with a history -- Beginning September 15th, this is how to "turn left" in Washington -- An old geological survey map of Washington and vicinity -- Wheels and roads make Washington a market.
    Subjects: George Washington University. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n2004121112 http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79041752; George Washington University. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00531730 http://id.worldcat.org/fast/533520; Travel. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01155558; Washington (D.C.) Description and travel. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145349; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - Washington society. Vol. 3, numbers 49 (Dec. 7, 1912)., Series 1; 7 pages: illustrations, portraits; 31 cm (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 321 FF
    Cataloging notes: Cover title.
    Subjects: Manners and customs. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01007815; Washington (D.C.) Social life and customs Periodicals.; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Periodicals. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01411641
  - Democratic standard and Whig of '76. Vol. 1, numbers 4 (May 12, 1846)., Series 1; pages [25]-32; 32 cm (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 322 FF
    Cataloging notes: Caption title.; Slavery in the District of Columbia (pages 26-28).
    Subjects: Antislavery movements United States Periodicals.; Slavery Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008111727; Antislavery movements. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00810800; Slavery. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01120426; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Periodicals. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01411641
  - Saks' souvenir: commemorating our 40th anniversary: Washington, D.C., September 30th, 1907., Series 1; 19 pages: illustrations; 31 cm (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 369 FF
    Cataloging notes: Caption title.; A brief history of our business / by Andrew Saks -- Forty years of the District / by Henry B.F. Macfarland -- The progress of banking in the District of Columbia / by John Joy Edson -- The work of forty years / by Thomas C. Noyes -- Washington forty years hence / by Henry Litchfield West -- The real estate business of Washington / by B.H. Warner -- The Washington Board of Trade / by George H. Harries -- The Washington public schools / by James F. Oyster -- The protection of the city of Washington for the last 40 years / by Richard Sylvester -- Concise history of electric service in Washington / by Edward S. Marlowe -- The Chamber of Commerce of Washington / by Robert N. Harper -- The fire department of Washington / by William T. Belt -- Transportation facilities / by George H. Harries -- Washington journalism, keeping pace with the city's growth / by Scott C. Bone -- Some inventions and discoveries of the last forty years / by H.S. Berliner -- Public buildings / by John J. Morrow -- Commercial Washington / by George C. Henning -- Some important happenings of the past forty years.
    Subjects: Saks & Company (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n84802071; Washington (D.C.) History. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145352
  - Holiday. Vol. 7, numbers 2 (Feb. 1950)., Circa [1950]; Series 1; 128 pages: illustrations (some color); 35 cm (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 374 FF
    Cataloging notes: Special Washington issue.; Washington / John Sayre -- Washington from the air -- Mr. President / Jonathan Daniels -- The Congress / Milton MacKaye -- The Supreme Court / Max Lerner -- The Negro -- Georgetown -- The press / A.J. Liebling -- Tourist Washington / John Horne Burns.
    Subjects: Travel. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01155558; Washington (D.C.) Description and travel. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145349; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - Holiday. Vol. 31, numbers 4 (April 1962)., Circa [1962]; Series 1; 195 pages: illustrations (some color); 35 cm (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 375 FF
    Cataloging notes: Special Washington issue.; Washington: the city of our time -- The birth and growth of a world capital / Charlton Ogburn, Jr. -- A stranger in the city / Aubrey Menen -- Lots to see in town / Ronald Searle -- John F. Kennedy: portrait of a president, part one / William Manchester -- The party circuit / Stephen Birmingham -- The unglorified civil servant / John D. Weaver -- The persuasive and enduring lobbyist / A.L. Todd -- The well-tempered politician / Tristram Coffin -- New faces from Africa / Peter Abrahams -- The antic arts / Peter Lyon -- The lordly journalists / Joe McCarthy -- Holiday handbook, Washington at work / Michael Frome -- The wondrous baseball Senators / Joel Sayre -- A capsule history of the First Ladies / Hugh G. Foster.
  - The Washingtonian: formerly the Mayflower log. March 1929., Circa [1929]; Series 1; 55 pages: illustrations, portraits; 31 cm (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 393 FF
    Cataloging notes: Caption title.; Program of inaugural events, March 4, 1929 -- This democratic world -- Inaugural snapshots.
    Subjects: Manners and customs. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01007815; Washington (D.C.) Social life and customs. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145361; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - U. States Military Asylum by Board of Commissioners of the Military Asylum., Circa [1852]; Series 1; 1 broadside; 30 x 25 cm (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 112 FF
    Cataloging notes: Caption title.; Schuyler Hamilton, Secretary.
    Subjects: United States Soldiers' Home. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n50066096; United States Soldiers' Home. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00516835
  - Dedication of the Lincoln Memorial, Washington, D.C., Decoration Day, MCMXXII., Circa [1922]; Series 1; 4 unnumbered pages: 1 illustration; 32 cm (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 120 FF
    Cataloging notes: Caption title (pages [3]).; Printed on double leaves.; Program.
    Subjects: Lincoln, Abraham, 1809-1865 Monuments Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79006779; Lincoln, Abraham, 1809-1865. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00030184; Lincoln Memorial (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85077136; Buildings. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00840962; Lincoln Memorial (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00999000; Monuments. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01025892; Washington (D.C.) Buildings, structures, etc. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008117388; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01204505
  - Central Park programme. Vol. 2, numbers 14., Circa [1868]; Series 1; 4 pages: illustrations; 36 cm (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 398 FF
    Cataloging notes: Caption title.; Program for concert in Central Park, with many advertisements.
    Subjects: Concerts. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85030620; Concerts. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00874069; Central Park (New York, N.Y.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85021920; New York (State) New York Central Park. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01316826; Advertisements. rbgenr; Programs. rbgenr
  - The Washington debutante. Vol. 2, numbers 2 (December, 1935), Christmas issue., Circa [1935]; Series 1; 32 pages: illustrations, portraits; 31 cm (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 250 FF
    Subjects: Debutantes Washington (D.C.); Debutantes. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00888892; Manners and customs. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01007815; Washington (D.C.) Social life and customs. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145361; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - Washington life. Vol. 4, numbers 9. Inauguration number with complete program., Circa [1905]; Series 1; 42 pages: illustrations, portraits; 36 cm (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 21 FF
    Subjects: Roosevelt, Theodore, 1858-1919 Inauguration, 1905.; Roosevelt, Theodore, 1858-1919 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00032496; 1905 fast; Presidents United States Inauguration. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106479; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075771; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155; Programs. rbgenr
  - Programme and inauguration souvenir: includes route of parade, hours and places of ceremonies, receptions, et cetera, with original portraits of Hon. Wm. McKinley and Hon. Garret A. Hobart., Circa [1897]; Series 1; 22 unnumbered pages: illustrations; 24 x 31 cm (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 39 FF
    Cataloging notes: Cover title: Program and souvenir of the inauguration, Hon. William McKinley, President of the United States of America, Hon. Garret A. Hobart, Vice President of the United States of America.
    Subjects: Hobart, Garret A. (Garret Augustus), 1844-1899. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n86001705; McKinley, William, 1843-1901 Inauguration, 1897.; Hobart, Garret A. (Garret Augustus), 1844-1899 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00177282; McKinley, William, 1843-1901 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00056763; 1897 fast; Presidents United States Inauguration. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106479; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075771; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155; Programs. rbgenr
  - Official program, inaugural ceremonies of John F. Kennedy, thirty-fifth President of the United States and Lyndon B. Johnson, thirty-seventh Vice President of the United States. Washington, D.C., January 20, 1961., Circa [1961]; Series 1; 63, 31 pages illustrations 29 cm (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 44 FF
    Subjects: Johnson, Lyndon B. (Lyndon Baines), 1908-1973. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/no2008089410; Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963 Inauguration, 1961.; Johnson, Lyndon B. (Lyndon Baines), 1908-1973. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00048810; Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00035588; 1961 fast; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Programs. rbgenr
  - The impact of African American architects on the cityscape of the nation's capital presented by Charles I. Cassell., Circa [1994]; Series 1; 1 portfolio; 29 cm (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 69 FF
    Cataloging notes: Talk presented at the Anacostia Museum, Smithsonian Institution, March 11, 1994.
    Subjects: African American architects Washington (D.C.); Architects Washington (D.C.); African American architects. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00799010; Architects. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00813114; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - President John F. Kennedy: 1917-1963., Series 1; 101 pages: illustrations (some color); 34 cm (Box 9, Folder 19)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 80 FF
    Cataloging notes: Cover title.; Nov. 29, 1963 issue of Life; includes articles on accused assassin Lee Harvey Oswald and Kennedy's successor Lyndon Johnson as well as those on Kennedy and his assassination.
    Subjects: Johnson, Lyndon B. (Lyndon Baines), 1908-1973. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/no2008089410; Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963 Assassination.; Oswald, Lee Harvey. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n50049686; Johnson, Lyndon B. (Lyndon Baines), 1908-1973. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00048810; Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00035588; Oswald, Lee Harvey. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00016900; Assassination. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00818962
  - Mrs. Kennedy, Caroline and John Jr. wait to join procession to Capitol., 1963; Series 1; 157, [3] pages: illustrations, portraits; 35 cm (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 81 FF
    Cataloging notes: Advertising throughout.; Cover title.; Issued as Life, volume 55, numbers 23, December 6, 1963.
    Subjects: Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963 Death and burial.
  - The Year in pictures., 1972; Series 1; 96 pages: chiefly illustrations (some color); 34 cm. (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 82 FF
    Cataloging notes: Last issue of Life (Chicago, Ill.), 1936-1972.
    Subjects: History Periodicals 1972.
  - My own story of the orbit by John Glenn., 1962; Series 1; 104 pages: illustrations (some color), portraits; 34 cm (Box 9, Folder 22)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 83 FF
    Cataloging notes: Cover title.; Issued as: Life, volume 52, numbers 10, March 9, 1962.
    Subjects: Glenn, John, 1921- http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n87878354; Glenn, John, 1921- fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00040914; Project Mercury (U.S.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n92071511; Project Mercury (U.S.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00679411
  - The Glenn story nobody saw: at home with Annie and the kids while John orbited the earth., 1962; Series 1; 94 pages: illustrations (some color), portraits; 34 cm (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 84 FF
    Cataloging notes: Cover title.; Issued as: Life, volume 52, numbers 9 March 2, 1962.
  - The space race is go: spaceman Glenn., 1962; Series 1; 82 pages: illustrations (some color), portraits; 29 cm (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 85 FF
    Cataloging notes: Cover title.; Issued as: Time, volume 79, numbers 9, March 2, 1962.
  - Joys of Christmas., 1972; Series 1; 134 pages: illustrations (some color); 34 cm (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 86 FF
    Cataloging notes: Cover title.; Issued as; Life, volume 73, numbers 24, Dec. 15, 1972.; Life special double issue.; Next to the last issue of Life (Chicago, Ill.), 1936-1972.
    Subjects: Christmas Pictorial works.; Christmas. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00859787; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - The Washington National Monument programme: Alexandria, Va., Februray 21 1885., Circa [1885]; Series 1; 1 sheet ([2] pages): illustrations; 31 x 25 cm (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 79 FF
    Subjects: Washington Monument (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh86000926; Washington Monument (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01170927; Programs. rbgenr
  - [Certificate from the District of Columbia Board of Education]., 1933; Series 1; 1 sheet; 36 x 42 cm (Box 9, Folder 27)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 207 FF
    Cataloging notes: Certificate awarded 1933, April 5, to Wallace S. Omohundro, Jr., by the Washington, D.C. Board of Education. He was appointed First Lieutenant of the High School Cadets of the District of Columbia. Certificate signed by Frank W. Ballou, Superintendent of Schools. Omohundro attended McKinley Technical School in Washington, D.C. His family lived at 2125 F St., NW, Washington, D.C.
    Subjects: Military cadets Washington (D.C.); Military cadets. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01021051; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - Mid-winter excursion to Washington D.C. via B. and O.R.R.: Thursday, Jan. 22, 1891., Circa [1891]; Series 1; 1 broadside: illustrations; 79 x 27 cm (Map-folder 1)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 396FF
    Subjects: Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n90615933; Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00535260; Railroads Timetables. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85111061; Railroads. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01088711; Travel. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01155558; Washington (D.C.) Description and travel. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145349; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Schedules. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01424357
  - Proclamation, 35th anniversary of the historic March on Washington Day, August 28, 1998 by Office of the Mayor, Washington, D.C., Series 1; 1 sheet; frame 33 x 49 cm (Map-folder 2)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 200
    Cataloger notes: Proclamation in honor of exhibition and symposium honoring the 1963 March on Washington for Jobs and Freedom.; Proclamation In honor of exhibition and symposium honoring the 1963 March on Washington for Jobs and Freedom: Looking Back ... Moving Forward: the March on Washington 35 Years Later.; Signed by Mayor Marion Barry.
    Subjects: March on Washington for Jobs and Freedom (1963: Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85080976; March on Washington for Jobs and Freedom. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01798999
- Ephemera, 1835-2002; Series 2
  This series contains large-size publications and printed materials covering the history of Washington DC and the Metropolitan area. More broadly the subject is American History. The images date from approximately 1835-2002.
  - Inaugural 1889 souvenir: a story of Airy Castle, the noted house in the tree-tops at Mt. Pleasant, Washington, D.C. sketches by W.H. Chandlee., Circa [1889]; Series 2; 32 pages: illustrations; 22 cm (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 1
    Subjects: Airy Castle (Washington, D.C.); Hayward, Allen B.
  - Inaugural ceremonies, March 4, 1889: committees in charge and rules for their government adopted by the executive committee, November 24, 1888., Circa [1888]; Series 2; 30 pages; 15 cm (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 2
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.
    Subjects: Harrison, Benjamin, 1833-1901 Inauguration, 1889.; Harrison, Benjamin, 1833-1901 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00008784; 1889 fast; Presidents United States Inauguration. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106479; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075771; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155
  - Program, inaugural ball, New Pension Building, March 4, 1889., Circa [1889]; Series 2; 16 pages; 11 cm (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 3
    Cataloger notes: Back cover has illustration of the interior of the Pension Building.; Cover title.
    Subjects: Harrison, Benjamin, 1833-1901 Inauguration, 1989.; Harrison, Benjamin, 1833-1901 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00008784; Pension Building (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh91002858; Pension Building (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00669375; 1989 fast; Presidents United States Inauguration. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106479; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075771; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155; Programs. rbgenr